<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>maven on Vaulttec</title>
    <link>http://vaulttec.org/tags/maven/</link>
    <description>Recent content in maven on Vaulttec</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://vaulttec.org/tags/maven/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sculptor</title>
      <link>http://vaulttec.org/project/sculptor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vaulttec.org/project/sculptor/</guid>
      <description>Sculptor is an open source productivity tool that applies the concepts from Domain-Driven Design and Domain Specific Languages.
You express your design intent in a textual specification (within an Eclipse editor), from which Sculptor generates (with a Maven plugin) high quality Java code and configuration. You can use the concepts from Domain-Driven Design (DDD) in the textual Domain Specific Language (DSL). E.g. Service, Module, Entity, Value Object, Repository.
The generated code is based on well-known frameworks, such as JPA, Hibernate, Spring Framework or Java EE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isis Script and Maven</title>
      <link>http://vaulttec.org/post/isis-script-and-maven/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vaulttec.org/post/isis-script-and-maven/</guid>
      <description>This post answers the question from issue #5 on how to generate Java code from an Isis Script file in a Maven build.
For using Xtext-based languages in Maven builds, the Xtext project provides a dedicated Maven plugin - xtext-maven-plugin. Here a Maven user just adds the corresponding Xtext language artifact as a dependency to this plugin and defines the language-specific configuration. This configuration contains the name of the StandaloneSetup class and the output folder.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>